tonight states the 24th of February 2016
we're we're just out doing a test drive
on a what's this thing called 68 GTO a
68 GTO made by Pontiac potty and did you
do what are you done too much a bit too
much yeah
oh this is amazing you can actually hear
percolating and doing something weird
what's it feel like oh that's probably a
good response II a bit responsible
so we're at a place called Loserville in
queensland yeah it's a nice place it's
raining our beer you know the real time
so the roads a bit slippery for the for
the weight on the back end of this so we
we can do 360s 720's but we could try it
the riches in the bottom that's the jda
the steering wheel he's hardly got any
of it look at it it's just thin whisper
yeah it guys pretty quick
big block a 400 big block now
what it what else here down there that's
been rebuilt so good nice toilet engine
each other
ten to one compression he beat worked
transmission speed all rebuilt so it's
good and then you fitted a cell to you
why did you do that
I wanted better economy better economy
yeah so that's what we're down a time
but just telling it and conning me run
but it sounds nice and it's running a
bit different yes yeah idling a lot
better yeah right away is right off the
back so don't want a whole lot better
alright i unite the road a new guys on
your way piss off and have some fun we
are okay all right talk to you later